var allQuestions = [

{					question: "Who is Mickey Mouse's girlfriend?",
					choices: ["Minnie", "", "Ariel", "Tinker Bell", "Alice"],
					correctChoice: 0
},

{					question: "Which sailor character would be lost without his can of spinach?",
					choices: ["Captain Hook", "Popeye", "Captain Jack", "Bluto", "Olive Oyl"],
					correctChoice: 1

},

{					question: "I am yellow and square. My best friend is a star shaped pink guy. We both live under the sea. Which cartoon character am I?",
					choices: ["Clarence", "Danny Phantom", "Dora the Explorer", "Scruffy", "Sponge Bob Square Pants"],
					correctChoice: 4
},

{					question: "I am part of a team of super sleuths who solve mysteries and chase monsters. Even though I am a dog, I can still speak, though not clearly. Who am I?",
					choices: ["Snoopy", "Pluto", "Scoopy Doo", "Underdog", "Goofy"],
					correctChoice: 2
},

{
					question: "I am coloured gray and love toying with bald hunters. What is my name?",
					choices: ["Caspar", "Magilla Gorilla", "Mickey Mouse", "Bugs Bunny", "Garfield"],
					correctChoice: 3
},

{
					question: "Which character does NOT belong?",
					choices: ["Pluto", "Goofy", "Minnie", "Snow White", "Road Runner"],
					correctChoice: 4
},

{
					question: "Which one of these is not one of Donald Duck's nephews?",
					choices: ["Huey", "Dewey", "Louie", "Joey"],
					correctChoice: 3
},

{
					question: "Which animated character is called The Lord of the Jungle?",
					choices:["Magilla Gorilla", "Tarzan", "Scar", "Mufasa", "Baloo"],
					correctChoice: 1
},

{
					question: "Who is Batman's side-kick?",
					choices: ["Superman", "Bat Girl", "The Hulk", "Robin", "The Joker"],
					correctChoice: 3
},

{
					question: "Who is the cute red-haired daughter of Wilma and Fred Flintstone?",
					choices: ["Betty", "Rose", "Bam-Bam", "Pebbles", "Minnie"],
					correctChoice: 3
},

{
					question: "In the cartoon The Jetsons, what is the name of the Jetsons' dog?",
					choices: ["Meteor", "Comet", "Jupiter", "Neptune", "Astro"],
					correctChoice: 4
},

{
					question: "Which one is Batman's arch-enemy?",
					choices: ["The Hulk", "Spider Man", "Superman", "The Joker", "The Green Goblin"],
					correctChoice: 3
},

{
					question: "Where do the Simpsons live?",
					choices : ["Springfield", "Smallville", "Krypton", "San Francisco", "Peoria"],
					correctChoice: 0
},

{
					question: "Pluto is the pet of which famous Disney character?",
					choices: ["Minnie", "Goofy", "Clarabelle", "Mickey", "Daffy"],
					correctChoice: 3
},

{
					question: "What does Bugs Bunny say in almost every cartoon he is in?",
					choices: ["That's all folks", "Take a left turn at Albequerque", "What's up doc", "Carrots are divine", "Ain't I a stinker"],
					correctChoice: 2
},

{			
					question: "What is Mario's occupation?",
					choices: ["Barrel Maker", "Plumber", "Baker", "Taxi Driver", "Progammer"],
					correctChoice: 1
},

{
					question: "This is a cartoon about a group of mutant superheroes which includes members Storm, Jubilee, Rogue and Gambit. What is the name of this team?",
					choices: ["The Avengers", "X-men", "Wonder League", "The Doom Patrol", "All-Star Squadron"],
					correctChoice: 1				
},

{
					question: "What flamingo-colored cat was a popular cartoon character in the 1970s?",
					choices: ["Garfield", "Cheshire Cat", "Snagglepuss", "Felix the Cat", "The Pink Panther"],
					correctChoice: 4
},

{
					question: "We were born in a lab. We come in a group of three. We are red, green and blue and have superpowers too! Which cartoon are we?",
					choices: ["The Teletubbies", "The Avengers", "The Powerpuff Girls", "Transformers", "X-Men"],
					correctChoice: 2
},

{
					question: "I am very short and I am a rodent. I have a best friend who looks almost exactly like me. What is my name?",
					choices: ["Mickey", "Minnie", "Jerry", "Dale", "Speedy Gonzales"],
					correctChoice: 3
},

{
					question: "Characters: Ash, Pikachu, Nurse Joy, Jesse. What show are they from?",
					choices: ["Transformers", "Looney Tunes", "Pokemon", "Simpsons", "The Jetsons"],
					correctChoice: 2
},

{
					question: "What was the name of Mickey's first cartoon to be featured in sound?",
					choices: ["What's Opera Doc", "Plane Crazy", "Steamboat Willie", "Bad Ear Day", "O Sole Minnie"],
					correctChoice: 2
},

];
